hello everybody
my name is robert elliott and i'm the
ceo
of manulife myanmar thank you all for
joining this webcast today
today's webcast is part of a series of
outreach programs
lined up to deepen our presence and
relationships with our customers
employees and partners in my life many
consider myanmar as a nation
insurance market that means new and that
is true
but only insofar as the recent history
is concerned
manulife is a testament to the rich
insurance heritage of this country
and with our first operations going as
far back as 1903
the first manual life insurance policy
in myanmar was sold
in november during the first year of
operations
117 years ago not many people
know that there was over a hundred
insurance companies in myanmar
between the late 19th century until the
1940s
and manulife was among those active in
shaping the industry
until its consolidation in the 1960s
the market commitment remained and
manulife was one of the first
to re-enter myanmar with their
representative office
in 2014. for many years until now
we have been steadfast in our mission
to share best practice reignite and
reshape the industry
to raise insurance literacy in my life
and today
we are delighted to announce that yet
another defining moment for manulife's
living history in this country as part
of our promise to make a difference
and be different we have partnered with
the custodians of the yangon central
railway station
to restore the yangon railway building
originally it was built
in 1877 but damaged during the world war
ii yangon central railway station
was rebuilt and completed in 1954.
the yangon railway building is an
extension of the station
and to this day houses hard-working
civil servants
managing the daily operations of the
station manulife has decided to breathe
new life into this historic building
because we believe
it's worth protecting this is our way of
fulfilling our purpose of preserving the
past
while protecting the future from myanmar
families
allow me to share this video documenting
the yangon railway building restoration
[Music]
foreign
impact is a core part of our commitment
to sustainability
touching every aspect of our business we
want to make every activity
every product to help make lives better
every day in every market we will let
our values guide the way we operate
and collaborate among these values these
three
best reflect the ethos behind the yangon
railway building restoration project
think big we believe that anything is
possible
and that we can always find a better way
own it we feel empowered to make
decisions
and take actions to deliver our mission
share our humanity in everything we do
we build a supportive diverse and
thriving environment
2020 was indeed thrown us a curveball
unlike any other over the past six
months
we have had to adapt live and work
amongst the covert 19 pandemic yet many
of the remarkable century-old buildings
you can find around yangon
humanity is resilient we will overcome
the crisis
and we will work together to rebuild
restore
and secure the future i'd like to thank
you all for listening
and we are very very excited about
re-entering the market here in myanmar
thank you thank you mr robert that's
really inspiring
tomorrow
[Music]
new life
addition